Key
[Music]
Record of drinking tea without sugar to keep wife company
We have to make your smiles bigger The record of looking at them There,
Gautam, keep breaking and making new colors of happiness The
eyes have seen
your smiles The record of going there was a request We have to
make a bigger record of returning home before the daughter goes to sleep
Gautam, keep making new colors of happiness Your
smiles, throughout
life We make records of small and big joys of our loved ones
For them, ICICI
Prudential Life Insurance's Lifelong
Lens so that they can keep making reports of happiness today, tomorrow and always